http://www.luckyfish.net/privacy-policy

Menu
Effective Date: 1/8/19This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.LuckyFish.com.
This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this
website, except where stated otherwise. It will notify you of the
following:What information we collect;With whom it is shared;How it can be corrected;How it is secured;How policy changes will be communicated; andHow to address concerns over misuse of personal data.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We
only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via
email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this
information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason
you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third
party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill
your request, e.g., to ship an order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future
to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this
privacy policy.Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do
the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or
phone number provided on our website:See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data.Security
We take precautions to protect
your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website,
your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data),
that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way.
You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of
your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address
of the web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted
online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who
need the information to perform a specific job (e.g, billing or customer
service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The
computers/servers on which we store personally identifiable information
are kept in a secure environment.Notification of ChangesWhenever material changes are made to the privacy notice specify how you will notify consumers.Orders
We request information from you on
our appointment deposit form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information
(like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit
card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing
purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an
order, we'll use this information to contact you.
Cookies
We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a
site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and
identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a
cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more
than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also
enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance
their experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to
any personally identifiable information on our site.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 1-805-962-7552 or via email to:
PatFish@LuckyFish.com.
